Yeah, it started.
Yeah, all right.
Let me know once my screen is visible.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, okay, so this is a very early draft.
Time and I had one discussion.
He shared some feedback.
So I want this more to be like a
conversation starter.
This is not like a final design that I'm
sharing with you.
No, just a question. Sorry to interrupt,
Jyotish,
since we are discussing this UX journey.
Shall we also include someone who is
going to implement this for the flow
agent?
Who is it?
Ohh.
Should.
No, the RAMALINGAM is is is to join.
RAMALINGAM primarily taking care of the
backend stuff, right?
But who will be implementing this from
the UA side?
Of.
I think he's added Santhosh and
Aleemullah on the call.
Okay, let me request to John.
Yes, bring someone,
otherwise it might be a surprise to them.
Mhm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, correct. So,
I'm trying to pull a limp.
Jyotish,
the overall experience would be aligned
with the current Bifrost UI, right?
Only the artifact data would differ from
Yes.
That's a ground rule, Sonal.
work.
Yes, we can't make anything different.
Yeah,
the experience should not be deviated
No,
since you mentioned that the experience
from launchpad.
is going to, yeah,
it's a different or something,
that's why you need UI people, right?
Yeah, let's see.
Yeah, definitely we need, no, my point is.
So something is specific to flow,
especially on the technical view, right?
And I don't know how that will be plugged
into this conversational window.
Somehow we have done this for workflow,
and I don't know whether we need to do
anything special,
but it will be always good if someone who
has to implement this and they can also
raise some concerns if they have anything
on the UX. That's my.
Primary int.
Right.
Okay.
Even otherwise, we have the recording if..
.
I think Ashok, yeah,
Ashok is also aware of correct Ashok
about the UI elements.
Yes, yes, yes, sir.
Okay, I think we can continue, Priya.
Prasad, if nobody is picking up your call,
leave it. Anyhow,
Yeah.
we are recording this meeting.
You can share the recording with them
Yeah.
later. We'll continue.
Okay, let's continue. I'm trying to pull.
They might join a bit late.
That's fine, yeah, that's fine. Go ahead,
Jyotish.
Let's continue. Yeah.
Okay.
So let's start with the prompt,
the sample,
like 3 prompts which Thanmayi shared.
So we start with that first one,
gain all Salesforce accounts with gain
site person.
So the same panel that we have for
launchpad and there'll be some reasoning
and.
It will ask you some questions if it's
not clear. Now,
these examples I've just borrowed from
the demo which Ramu had shared earlier.
So it's going to ask you these questions
and you can answer it conversationally.
Once you get this response,
there are multiple things can happen.
So right, I mean,
there could be some cases where it's very
clear the agent is going to know that
this is something that can be built only
with a flow service.
You can't use a workflow.
And in some cases,
it might also see what you have been
using.
If a user has always been creating flow
services or some logic has to be built.
basis which recommendation should come in.
So that is my first question, Jyotish,
since you gave the prompt.
Yes.
What is the starting point?
I opened the window, the chat window,
Huh?
and you gave the prompt.
And how this agent will decide.
Mhm.
whether this is a workflow or flow.
Should we even have that question?
Because today we are supporting only
workflow,
so there is no clarification is required.
But tomorrow when we bring flow agent,
Mmh.
then there might be some confirmation is
required from the user.
If I specifically mention create a flow
service.
With this use case, then it is clear,
but if I give a prompt directly.
Somewhere it should be instructed, right?
So maybe you can add a note.
Yes, so, so this is already there, Tom.
Like, for example,
We need to see.
once I've answered these questions,
I've said, OK, this looks like something,
like some example I put,
and I recommend that we use a flow
service to handle this reliably. OK, so...
So,
who will who will decide and how this
will be decided? That's my question.
The agent will decide.
what data will pack this up.
Next question.
So looking at the prompt,
you should be able to tell, right?
Like there'll be some cases where you can
build that same automation using a
workflow and a flow service.
But in some cases,
maybe you can only build it using a flow
service. That could be one. Second,
I was thinking is if I, if as a user,
I mostly create flow services.
Then I should be default.
No,
I'm just trying to help the engineering
team in order to classify how this
decision can be arrived.
Mhm.
Maybe based on the connector availability
across different flavors or account
availability, I don't know,
but I'm just giving a heads up.
If this has to be handled,
some intelligence to be built.
Mm.
Behind the scene.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah,
and and also who will do it is a big
question, right, Dam? Like,
is it within the scope of a flow agent,
RSC?
Is it that AICS team who is handling it
will decide,
and then and and then it handles to?
Flow agent, so that is also a question,
right?
Yeah,
so this is where I wanted a master agent
for integration itself.
Mm.
Behind the master agent,
there will be workflow agent, flow agent,
and in future I can also have runtime
management agent, right?
Something behind the scene of the
integration agent that's simply making
some decision.
But today we don't have that layer.
All our agents are directly plugged into
the other layer.
There is one more agent.
I don't know which agent, but in between,
in front of that,
we have the bifrost agent.
And bifrost agent,
maybe we need to discuss with them,
Ramu or someone.
Somewhere this decision has to be arrived.
Or if the user directly start clicking
the flow service action,
then there is no such question.
Yeah, go ahead, Sonal.
Tom, there would be a preference, right?
Like when you are under the flow service
page and user initiate a chat,
the context would be helpful there.
Second, every data,
I mean all the data connector related
specifically, we are dumping into UAC.
Correct.
So UAC integration should be both in
workflow agent and flow service agent.
And explicitly, one should be prioritized,
right?
Like if it goes to a workflow agent and
if it doesn't finds the connector, so...
I mean, behind the scene,
it should not be shown to the user.
It could be like a background processing
happening,
like which connector is meant for what,
and then the final outcome would be there.
An agent says that, workflow agent says,
okay, it can't handle the request.
Flow service can handle it,
and then it can be back with back back
with the flow if user is not explicitly
right writing that it it is a flow
service or a workflow,
but for the phase one,
what do you what do you feel like the
experience which we are talking about?
on the choice of selecting a workflow or
flow service.
Should it be upfront or we have to apply
the, I mean,
intelligence at that layer as well for
the first cut, phase one.
So, my for first cut,
maybe we can start with the flow or
workflow.
And all these intelligence can be built
in the super layer. I want that layer.
And behind that layer,
we will plug all the other agents,
workflow agent, flow agent,
and the future agents.
And the decision has to be made at the
parent layer. Okay. But for the...
immediate milestone one,
if we couldn't achieve this,
maybe we need to take the direct route.
Okay. User, take the decision.
He wants to create flow.
Then he tells this explicitly.
And click that particular action,
and then start conversing with an agent
that that route we can take. OK,
add a note here,
Jyotish will revisit this, find a way.
Yeah.
And then the journey can start, yeah.
So I have a thought on that, Prasad.
If you see all of our prompts,
even in the prompt library,
or like when you see the way people are
typing,
I don't know whether they will type build
a workflow versus a flow service.
What if they just say I want to build
this automation?
So we have to think if the intelligence
layer that Tom is talking about doesn't
Correct, correct.
exist on day one,
we still have to tell them that, okay,
we have two available, like, no options.
This flow service does this,
workflow does this. You make a selection.
If we can't build our intelligence.
Because yes,
if they write in the prompt itself that I
want to build a workflow,
that is the easiest way to go ahead,
right? But what if they don't?
We need to have a fallback then.
Yeah, yeah. So, Tom,
shall we create one epic mostly for AICS
team, right?
To take this kind of a decision,
either to choose the workflow agent or a
flow agent.
Shall we create an epic and then hand it
over to them?
Yeah, we can, we can have one.
Yeah.
But is it like UAC,
we need to then push all the intelligence
to the UAC,
right from the connectors to the existing
flow service or something. So.
Yeah, so take a case,
the connector metadata,
my assumption is that in which flavor
this connector is applicable. Flow,
workflow, Dev, something like that, right?
So if we have that intelligence as part
of the connector metadata,
then we should be able to arrive to this
conclusion.
But it's a predefined intelligence,
but I'm thinking even beyond, right?
Okay.
If the agent can decide what will best
fit,
Absolutely.
even if these connectors are available
across different integration flavors,
based on our historical pattern.
Maybe the agent should suggest, okay,
this might be a best fit for this use
case, something like that.
Maybe that is future goal,
not immediate target,
but that's how I want to achieve in the
future. But for now,
we can go with some static intelligence.
Okay, so for Q3, let's proceed with that,
some kind of a static intelligence.
Yeah.
We'll create an epic and then we'll
target it for Q4.
Yep, agree.
Yeah.
Okay.
So,
say user has said continue with flow
service,
in which case we will first ask for a
project.
This I think we also touched upon this
topic yesterday in our discussion.
And in Launchpad,
I've seen that we are for workflow
creation also we are asking for a project.
So this is the first selection.
If agent is again intelligent enough,
it should be able to recommend one.
project and continue. If not,
then it should recommend that these are
like few projects you can select bases,
whatever reason,
like you know these accounts are already
set up or whatever reason that's there.
Post project selection.
We'll see a business view;
technical view is not there right now,
but you'll see some kind of a business
view,
which will give you a high-level logic of
how this flow service would, you know,
look like,
and then there has to be certain
configuration which has to be done.
conversationally and the user has to
answer all of those things on chat.
And once that validation is done,
you will get to see a technical view.
It's basically a representation of the
current existing technical view.
We have some other account authoring
buttons and all, but I've.
Just skip one for the mapping.
So if you click on that,
you will see the mapping on the same
workspace view.
Once you are happy with this,
you can continue typing,
you can continue playing around with it.
And once you're happy,
you can say create flow service.
which will then create the flow service
and then you can test it.
And if the test is successful,
I'll need here, I'll need help with, like,
you know,
the design for the test report in a flow
service,
but once you're happy with the flow
service you have tested,
everything is working fine,
you can then I,
the agent will give you a suggestion that
I can deploy it on your preferred,
you know, runtime this cloud runtime or...
you can select a different runtime.
So if you want to continue with cloud
runtime,
you continue it and it gets executed.
It will give you a link on the of where
to find on the product.
And if you decide to change the, you know,
select a different runtime,
you can give the options on the chat
itself and user can select and.
deployed.
So this is the flow that we have right
now. I think there are a lot of,
maybe there are a lot of other complex
use cases that we have not covered,
but at a very happy path,
I think this is what we wanted to share
So what is this action shown at the
bottom? Create new flow service.
with you.
Now this is a new conversation, is it?
Yeah, yeah, you can start a new one, um,
and yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, understood. Okay.
Any questions, comments?
Yeah.
No open for question.
So in the business view,
the agent has to give the business view.
Is it typically how that should happen?
I think Sonal you can explain that
because you have done that for workflow
already.
So,
business view is equivalent to planner
data,
which we are generating Prasad over here
in workflow.
How it happens is we have steps like step
one is your trigger node,
step 2 is your action node,
step 3 is loop node, and so on. So, but...
Okay.
But in flow, the icons, Jyotish,
what are they?
Mhm.
They are the placeholder for icon or are
we expecting?
Yeah, these are placeholder for icons,
so that's what I wanted to also like
discuss, like, you know,
the business view for a flow service,
because I noticed that in the flow
service we have,
we I didn't see icons right,
the the visual representation is a little
different, so yeah,
this this I wanted to discuss.
Correct.
Do we have icons that we can use or do we
have to do this just pure text? Also,
what do we put in the text? I mean,
this is, again,
I picked this directly from Rama's demo.
So whether we'll be able to have a
heading, a name of a node and description,
because there we are not showing error
handling and those other details,
but if that is required, not required,
I think that's all we need to discuss.
Okay,
but what is the point is like we in
planner, that is a mermaid diagram, right?
If you have seen that.
So it is also representing the flow going
from where to where,
like a loop is happening and if.
condition is met, then it proceeds to map.
But if not met, like else part,
then how we can go back to the previous
loop and verify the next step.
Like if you're skipping the execution on
failure.
or are you continuing the execution on
failure? So.
So, yeah, so that's why.
It is a graphical structure.
Yeah,
so I had the same conversation with Tam.
Like there were two parts.
If you remember the demo,
there was a moment diagram and then there
were steps,
I think execution steps or something,
which was a list of things.
So what I've done is I'm assuming the
list of steps are things that we are
doing. So I've just put that. But again,
that's a good question.
If it, if it is actually a linear process,
will our user be able will see this and
really be able to visualize what the,
you know, flow service is gonna look like,
or do we need to add, like,
if or it will be a non-linear flow,
in which case we might have to, like,
you know...
like make some minor modifications to the
business view. That's open for discussion.
Yeah, and the same for workflows.
So today also we are only showing the
node, like loop, that's it.
What is happening inside the loop node,
we are not actually showcasing the
business or technical business plan data
to the user today.
So we may need to make it.
more graphical rather than linear.
So maybe we can think on it.
Plus showing icon,
is it required because these are the
certain steps.
So loop and if you have seen in flow
service,
you won't be getting any icon data there.
For Salesforce.
Ohh.
And wherever the application name is
there, we can bring that icon.
But what is the utility of showing the
icon on top of each step? Is it required?
So, it's, yeah,
so mostly it is to just keep the,
you know,
designs consistent with the workflow.
So we don't want to create different
designs.
We want to create something which is
similar.
If there are icons that we need to create
for a few, maybe we could consider that.
But what you are recommending, like,
you know,
it doesn't show certain details and all.
And if that requires us to revisit the
business view,
then we might have to make that
consistent for workflow as well.
And again, Thanmayi,
you can like share your thoughts on this.
Yeah,
I'm still processing what Sonal raised
earlier, right?
So this is a linear representation,
but in real time,
if we expand this view to represent
whatever the data we have to communicate,
then it will be mostly aligned with
technical view. It should not be.
Right, say, for example, the if condition,
and there is an else condition,
and where this else will be fit.
Right? And similarly, the try-catch block,
are we going to represent those things?
I don't know.
And that part we have to think.
And do we really need to show everything
in the business view?
That is my other question.
Because business view at the high level.
We are going to show, okay,
how this integration is going to look
like at the higher level,
not at the deep dive level.
Deep level will be in the technical view.
Ohh.
Do we even need to show the if condition
loop and all? That's my part.
No,
I think as part of the demo what Rama has
shown, right, there are some steps.
Step one, step 2,
whatever kind of a thing.
It's kind of an algorithm, right?
Can we just show those steps? Can we?
These are those steps.
I'm just copied those steps. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I understand. Correct,
correct. So, anyway,
because that is going to be sequential,
so...
Yeah.
I'm just thinking, you see,
otherwise it becomes complicated.
Assume that whatever the steps which are
shown sequentially are going to come here
horizontally, that's it.
Hey, Rama, please go ahead.
Sorry, I joined a little late.
The point what I was trying is the reason
behind showing the if condition,
all those things are stamped.
Just to give a double confirmation for
the user,
I have considered those important things,
right?
The person who is doing might be a
business user, correct?
That's the reason we are showing that
business view there.
So we have to double confirm him in his
language where he can understand. Look,
I'm going to,
I will ensure that I will go through all
your records and I will respect your
conditions, etc. and other things.
So that is that is the thing.
And another another thing is map all
Just to answer this, Ramu,
just hold your thoughts.
things.
Just to answer your first question,
our first statement,
I slightly differ from that,
meaning the flow service is primarily
targeted for the technical user, right,
not the business user.
But only we are enabling the technical
user to achieve certain task using agent.
So in that case, now my thought is, okay,
for workflow,
we are representing the whole intent at
the high level with certain boxes and
some information.
And if he wanted to see a detailed
information,
he has to go to the technical view and
there we are showing the actual workflow.
Here.
This primary persona is none other than...
the technical user, the developer.
And if we render a business view,
my recommendation is it should be high
level, because anyhow,
if he wanted to see the detailed view,
there is a technical view next to this
business view, right? And he can see that.
But if you represent the business view
also, then it should be meaningful.
So when you say if...
and without the else.
Then it will confuse where the else will
fit here if I have a flow with the else
also.
No, Dan, I get it, Dan.
That's the reason we have been spending
so much time to make it make all those
things.
And that is the reason we added that
error handling, try catch, et cetera,
the understanding the technical audience,
et cetera. To answer your question,
Uh-huh.
Okay.
that is the reason we added so many
things into this.
But it is when we say business.
I don't know whether the business view is
the right acronym for this case or
anything. It is basically at a high level.
I'm showing you the flow chart, right?
Correct.
And that's the reason we have made all
this. So it's a flow chart.
The reason behind that is, see,
what is that additional value we have to
bring for the persona?
That persona is already smart, right?
And this is Jyotish,
I want to discuss with you.
There are two ways a developer will,
sorry to divulge stamp, but I want to,
this is the right topic that Sangam. See,
there are two ways a developer will write
Mm.
a code, right? One is following the SDLC,
which is basically I gather the
requirements,
I understand the requirements,
I go from there and I do that, right?
But this persona when he sees.
he would expect, oh,
first show me what you have.
Show me the code, right?
Something that is, that is,
there is a different set of developers
there, right?
No.
Where they'll be immediately,
they would love to see what is the output.
And from there they will say, hey,
can you correct this?
Can you correct this?
Can you correct this? So there are two,
two kind of persona experience itself
there.
Right.
That is something I don't know whether
you already thought about it.
That is also I was mulling around today
to see if there is something we can do or
anything like that. But Tam,
I agree to you.
But the thing here is at a very high
level,
we so else and all will show them the we
would have asked the questions and.
So Rama, one question to you,
since you did some research on this,
in this diagram,
we are showing something on the second
text, right? First icon,
then the primary text,
and the secondary text.
So will you be able to...
get those intelligence also every time.
If there is a if else,
then try catch and all those things.
If that is possible,
then I recommend to have the else
condition can be mentioned as a secondary
text below the if.
Yeah, yeah, we can do that.
We can do that.
Yeah, then then I'm good.
This will give a clear picture for me.
Yeah.
But we didn't think about icon, right?
Like Prasad was saying,
the thought process for us are step by
step, like how a flow works, right?
Flow doesn't work horizontal,
flow works vertical.
So that is where we thought.
Now when you are bringing this into a
horizontal environment,
that's where the user experience we have
defined. And the second user experience,
which I definitely want to think about
and hear your thoughts is.
How would a developer will do that, right?
Because they will jump and try to see an
output and from there they want to edit
so that they feel like they are
contributing more into that, right?
That is one thought.
The second thought is, hey, you know what?
Technically you are strong.
I'm not going to bother you there,
but business analysis wise,
I will help you.
That is the reason the questioning still
we are making it strong and we are asking
so many relevant questions as applicable,
et cetera, and other things.
So what is that persona level experience
is something I would request if you
already thought about it, fine.
That is one thing.
I just want you to please think on it,
mull on it, and...
You have a lot of people,
developers there, just check them that.
Another thing is...
Sure.
Yeah, good, good, good.
Yeah, may I proceed? Yeah,
another thing is how the approval
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, please.
happened, Jyotish,
because we have to show this and do an
approval, right?
Then only the technical view goes,
or we just we just continue from there,
because this is the responsible part,
right? We just want to make sure.
I think that step happened a little
earlier, I believe. We are...
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, so, so now...
That was my question.
Are we taking that approval in the
previous? I don't remember that.
No,
but before showing the before showing the
Yeah, yeah, so, so,
so can you go go to the next screen? No,
plan, you know, before.
can you go to the next screen?
A previous.
Before or after previous?
Previous, previous screen.
No,
here we are selecting the project next.
Only the Rajat.
Next.
This is a preview. Next,
continue with the validation.
After the validation, then our workflow,
we used to have one action, right?
Create workflow.
That is that.
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, so, so, so after I click.
Grill for service.
Then only this will be created.
By this time,
I will have my technical views ready.
No, no, I won't have that time,
because first I want to make sure user
approves the plan before I do the heavy
lifting of taking the grammar,
mulling on that grammar,
doing all those things, right?
Because the technical view is basically
an iframe of example I'm saying,
iframe of the actual flow, correct?
I don't want to spend time on that.
Unless I know whether I have understood
the problem statement correctly or not,
so can you please go, Jyotish?
I'm back.
I'll okay.
You have that recording right?
Where here we have to say, hey,
this is what the plan could you approve
or modify, right?
So this we give the user the liberty
rather than we spending,
we spending up on another agent to do
that, etc. and other things.
So please think about it. And then.
Rama one point.
No, Rama, one question.
If I'm not okay with this proposed plan,
the business view,
then I can still modify using a
You can modify.
conversation.
I don't need anything from the agent.
Yes, yes.
I'll just tell, okay? And once this, yeah,
I saw that.
In the demo I showed you, right?
In the demo I showed you,
What I'm saying is after this view is
generated, I'll go through that.
that modification.
and I'm now fine,
then I'll do a validation.
Validation will do the account and
everything is properly selected and set
for this thing. Once everything is set,
then this create flow will come.
By the time this flow is ready and I can
see the technical view and then.
When I click create view, create flow,
then this flow will be actually created.
Until then,
it's all in memory manipulations.
No, what is what is technical view here?
It's the actual flow, correct?
Not the actual flow. Flow is not created.
It is a representation of your intent.
How is it different from a business view
then? Because what I have...
The.
No business, no,
this is a full grammatical representation.
Business view at the high level,
some dummy boxes. OK, just to illustrate.
OK, this is what we are going to do,
but this one you can see the mapping and
Mm.
everything.
Okay,
I have set all these things just to
Ohh.
verify. Once I'm done,
then I can click create flow.
So.
So Jyotish,
can you update it as an example for the
same thing, this technical view,
the business view, whatever we have,
can you convert that into a technical
view so at least I have an understanding?
And Sonal,
today what I heard is for workflow,
you are just taking the actual workflow
and showing in technical view, right?
Is it not the case?
Yes,
so in technical view is the actual
workflow. Basically,
we could put a workflow which is in draft
Correct.
state.
So there are certain states which we have
Yeah.
given.
It's like draft state and once user says,
okay, everything is good,
you can create a workflow.
Then only that workflow will be converted
from draft.
To non-drop,
like it would be pushed to the.
No, understood, understood, Sonal,
but there is there is a heavy lifting
which is happening where the entire
process we are doing without even user
confirming that they are okay with it,
correct? Even if it is in the draft mode,
it is in the draft mode. So my point is,
we show the business view,
ask for users approval,
and then do the technical view.
Actually,
we had this discussion with Keesa when we
had the initial design right.
So what we said,
Okay.
So, what?
business view would get generated.
Technical will only generate once
everything is, you know,
confirmed by the user.
Correct.
But then the point was,
we are showing business view. It's very,
you know.
A high level as Sam is pointing out,
like it should be very high level,
it should not give you more technical
data.
Technical view is the actual
representation of your artifact,
like the technicality,
the mapping and all. So for flow service,
I feel anyway that business view which we
are generating for flow.
Pro service, it's a plan, it's a step of,
I mean,
the algorithm data technical view we can
generate or not that I will that I think
Ashok can answer, but Jyotish before that,
like...
Before we create a workflow, right,
there is a state where we are not
generating a technical view.
It is just a business view is only
Yes, which is even here,
so after validation.
generated.
Correct.
After validation and if you've configured
everything that is when you generate a
technical view. Now I had a related.
Sorry, Jyotish, just to just to be clear,
when you say validation,
Yeah.
what is the validation here?
Because it is not clear.
You are saying you are checking for
account or anything or you as a user I'm
approving the plan.
What do you mean by validation here?
You're not approving a plan. Yeah,
you're looking for accounts,
Mm.
you're looking for like missing lookups
and all and then...
Those are all those are all internal,
right?
Those are all we don't need to get an
approval from the user.
Those are a mandatory steps.
See today what is happening here is if
you if you see the video there,
it starts with integration pre,
I forgot that, precondition check.
So there in the precondition check,
we are validating all these things. So.
So, this...
Those are all those are all not this.
If you see the video there or I can show.
Eng.
This is questioning.
This is questioning after.
No, no, no, before questioning itself,
we have a validation step.
Ohh.
Let me quickly show you.
What validation?
I will show you, I will show you,
I will show you.
In the winter, Pradeep,
you have a question.
Arfath.
Sorry, you are seeing my screen? So here,
I mean,
Oh, yes, yes.
we are happy to modify however we want to.
Just a thought. See,
what happens is here we have the
precondition check where we check for
whether that account is there.
All those information are there.
I know we haven't integrated the USC,
so we have some dummy account as a on the
on the local mock mock API and we are
doing it.
So we do that check prior itself and
everything pass only then we start asking
the questions. So why can't it be there?
And we just ask the user to approve the
plan. So here if we are,
what we are asking is like this.
Hey, I...
But that is still conversational, OK?
No, no, only one place we are asking,
right?
And we are very clearly saying what are
you approving?
When you say validation,
I don't understand what is the validation
Okay.
So.
there.
Am I validating the plan or like Jyotish
said,
I'm validating the account or is it
everything?
So here I should not ask the user about,
it's a mandate.
I have to validate account.
I have to validate all those things.
I should not even ask the user to do that.
What I have to use, ask the user is.
Are you approving it or not? Right?
So that is the thing.
And here it also tells the next step.
So that I will be very clear about my
next step. Look, once you approve,
these are the next steps I'm going to do.
So a user is very clear about.
Six.
So, one, one point, Ramu,
so can you share your screen again?
Oh yeah, yeah, sorry.
So, what my understanding was...
The steps will be represented as a
business view, okay,
Tax.
in a high level boxes and some text.
And then you have 3 follow up action,
Got it.
right?
The next actions and any of that can be
represented. But this approve or modify.
It's not explicit, but if I'm okay,
I will select any one of the proposed
action. If not,
I will converse again and continue my
edit. That's how this whole thing will go,
right?
So this approve yes or no will not be
there.
But it is implicit.
No,
there are three advantages you get with
that, TAM. One,
what you are doing today is you are
Okay.
saying continue the validation, correct?
That is what you are asking,
which is not clear, at least for me.
Maybe I don't have background or anything.
Second thing.
No, this is on the business view, right?
Correct, correct, correct.
Second advantage what I get is the reason
Ohh.
why I'm asking this is I'm going to log
it and tomorrow I can build a feedback
P.
loop.
I know what are the plans that got
approved directly and what are the plans
the user modified and there are a lot of
very good libraries available to in
machine learning to feedback.
Okay.
And we can build a feedback loop and
continue to improve on it.
Yeah.
And there are automated feedback loops
also available. So for that,
Anand.
I need to know whether the user is okay,
because the plan represents whatever the
Yeah.
user is trying to do.
I understood the intent.
I understood what the connectors can do,
what the connectors cannot do.
what objects available,
what objects not available.
Everything is summarized.
I know this is a,
I'm doing some testing so you can see
some issues,
but this is what it is showing.
So my part is, look,
whatever synopsis I'm giving it to you is
coming up with a lot of things.
Once I know I approve,
once let's say if user modifies
specifically if condition.
I know that, oh,
this is the area I have to improve.
So that is another thing for me.
So this is a wonderful opportunity,
one to get a feedback,
one to be very clear about what is that
I'm trying to do.
And you said need not worry about account
validation, et cetera, and other things.
Those are all preconditions.
So everything starts from there only.
So I don't want to start with the.
Nothing. So that is that is a thought.
I mean, I'm okay to do however it is,
but this is a thought I just want to
share.
This is very valid, Ramu.
Nothing is non-valid. It's valid point.
But I'm thinking slightly different.
So even today,
if we represent this action slightly
differently,
you can capture those information.
Say for example,
you are proposing certain next set of
actions based on your
Score or your decision tree, right?
You have proposed something and now you
are taking some next course of action for
the user to take and you are proposing
something,
which means these are your highly rated
next set of actions.
If I select some action, which means...
Internally you can understand, okay,
my proposed plan is accepted and user is
taking action on my proposed action.
No, human,
human in the human in the feedback
doesn't work like that, Tam.
How many times in real world do you think,
unless I ask,
you would have interrupted and you would
have even read about it?
So this this kind of puts in in in puts
up what do you call a subtle indication
to the user.
Please read it above, right?
So this double comes some,
so the in the human in the,
and this is this is how the human in the
loop will do that, right?
We don't assume things.
So if we can do that, I'm fine.
Okay, if we can do that intelligence, I'm,
but we should not, sorry.
Which one you are saying?
Sorry, which intelligence you are saying?
So, this...
What do you, what do you,
what do you say this?
So this can also be an action, right?
The yes, no, something like that.
It's an action.
Isn't it?
However you want it, see,
we have done it like that,
but if you want a button,
we can put a button.
We already had a button,
but we removed it for some purpose.
I forgot that. So however you want it,
we can do it. So I know when we are.
Yeah, so so so what am I thinking is,
okay,
launchpad expect some representation of
the conversation.
And they also have a certain pattern for
the actions. Now,
we have both actions as well as this
confirmation.
So this is slightly different pattern,
but we can get the sign up from Keesa.
It's not a big deal. Okay,
I'll have a conversation with that.
with her and get that confirmed.
But my point is, if we can plug this.
the confirmation as an action,
then there is no deviation from what we
are already having, isn't it?
Sorry, when you say action,
you are saying like a button,
suggested actions.
So, yeah,
so the button we are representing that as
a button,
but that's what my proposed actions,
right? The next course of action.
Yeah, that that we already have it.
I don't know if there is a local.
Is there any environment Ashok or Sonal?
Do you have it with the button?
Yeah.
We did with we did that and we removed it,
right?
No, actually, right.
So suggested actions are the course of
action which are suggested.
Like user can still choose something else
and type in and proceed. But over here,
or Tom,
we are asking user to either approve and
deny, or I mean, yes or no, or modify.
Or modify.
Like without that,
we won't be able to proceed to the next
course of tool.
So, so let me ask further dig deeper.
I have only, okay,
my time is over already.
I have to go for the other meeting,
Ha ha ha!
but I'll quickly close my question.
My question is, yes.
Yeah, organizer,
I should sorry to interrupt.
Organizer has to tell your time is over,
so,
but you yourself is telling interesting.
You are under so much.
No.
No,
this meeting is scheduled only for 30
Singh.
minutes. We are already overrunning.
Iyer.
Yeah, yeah.
No, no, Tom, I'm just pulling your leg.
I said generally the person who is
Everybody is doing that same, no.
It's not new to me.
inviting.
Everybody is pulling my legs, OK? So,
Ramu.
Uh, alright, I think.
Okay, okay, let's work.
I never do. See, Sam, I never do that. OK.
Ah.
Mhm.
OK, so, so, but Pradeep, we are friends.
and we are on record. Okay,
let me come back to the conversation.
My question to you, Ramu,
I'm okay to have this confirmation.
Yes, no and continue or change,
modify something like that. If I say yes.
What it will do, and if I say no.
what the next set of actions it will
happen. And if I have to say modify,
and now I'll continue the conversation
and make some changes to this current
context.
Right?
So yes means it will create the flow.
No means what?
Correct.
No one modify are almost the same.
Ahh.
It's just a it's just a user experience
wise we will show you when you say modify.
Yeah,
we will brainstorm this a little bit.
Sure.
I'm working to have this because this
will reiterate what the engine proposed
and what the user take the action, right?
And based on that,
if you want to build an intelligence
behind the scene, I'm fine.
We can have it.
But we have to have a proper
representation of this,
the decisions node bit.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll quickly tell one thing alone.
What we are doing here is when you say
yes, you're obvious.
It will go to the next tool and it will
continue with it. When you say modify,
it will ask you where I have to modify.
Our user can say modify hyphen and then
write whatever paragraph they want to
write. When they say no,
currently it is going to exit. We are.
The thought is like, okay,
user does not want to continue.
So we'll ask, hey,
I understand you're not happy with it.
Would you like to go with a different
prompt or something like that? But we can,
No, by mistake, by mistake, if I said no,
but I want to continue.
we can.
Then you can again say the context is
still there.
No, that's a problem.
You should not lose the whole
conversation and get...
No, no, I won't lose, I won't lose.
The context is still there, unless,
Yeah, this is just.
unless user says user type a new new
prompt, it won't, it won't go away,
even if user is trying to edit also,
it won't go away, so edit,
Okay.
so this will come under the edit intent.
So, what would happen is, sure.
Okay.
Yeah,
maybe I need to have one discussion with
you separately, Ramu,
to understand this a little bit,
because we can have it. I mean,
I'm not very particular about, okay,
restricted use.
We should always go with the pattern.
If something is beneficial for our future
improvement, we should.
Sumit.
do that. I'm okay with that.
And I can get the sign up from who needs
to be informed.
I'll talk to them and get the sign up.
But I need to understand and get the
buy-in before I take that to them. Okay.
Sure.
Yeah, only one thing I am.
Let's align one. Sorry,
I know we have run out of time,
IT.
I am out tomorrow.
but let's align ones internally before
sharing it externally with anyone.
So let's internally align it, capture it,
and then let's share it with others,
just so that it doesn't look like we are
not alignable.
Only for the final confirmation bit,
nothing else.
Everything else, we are good, I believe.
Sorry, which one?
Which one you are saying?
Which which one you are saying?
I don't have. Sorry, you're saying?
So.
We just showed a demo.
We didn't share anything.
No, based on your...
No, no, no,
I'm not because I am telling time, yeah,
We didn't share anything.
No.
No, no, no,
he's talking about user journey, Sharma.
the journey, yeah, yeah, yeah,
so whatever we have discussed, let's...
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
No,
based on your screen sharing and last
Thanks.
time you had a last bit rate,
the confirmation bit,
only that we need to have an internal
meeting. But other than that,
the general flow,
I don't think we have confusion.
Maybe because Ramu mentioned that he
wants to ask the validation upfront,
No, I I want to see the recording.
right? And in Launchpad,
we are asking to create that validation
is happening, right? That okay,
create workflow as a next step.
Or you are saying, okay,
are you ready to continue?
Okay.
It's happening towards the end.
So there's a big gap asking upfront
Okay, let me propose one thing.
There are two action item.
versus asking later.
No, no, another another thing,
sorry to interrupt, sorry, Tom,
One minute I have to drop now.
I'll propose one thing for a next set of
before I forget, sure, sure.
action. Sonal action number one.
You go through this flow proposal and
compare this proposal with your workflow
journey. And if you find any deviations,
we need to cover that in the next meeting.
Okay, that is action number one. Second,
whoever needs to implement for the flow
service,
they have to digest the information flow.
And if there is a challenge technically
to meet this requirement,
then they have to come back and tell what
are all the challenges and why that can't
be solved. Okay, two actions.
Third actions,
we have to have one more discussion
internally to brainstorm a little bit on
validate.
as well as this bit, final bit,
the confirmation bit.
These 3 actions we'll check and we'll
conclude this meeting. Is this fine?
Yeah,
just one thing I want to give heads up.
I am out Friday, Monday, and Tuesday,
so we can have it only.
I don't know whether it is going to have
any impact, Prasad. That's...
No,
we'll continue our discussion tomorrow.
That's fine. Based on these items, right?
One,
we will compare with the flow journey and
see if there are any discriminancies.
Maybe Jyotish,
you can also maybe quickly spend some
time. The other thing, second is what,
Tam, you said?
So, second is,
whoever needs to implement this flow
agent UI,
they have to digest this information,
Ohh.
whatever Jyotish has drafted,
and they have to come back and tell if
Okay.
there are any technical challenges.
Okay.
Okay, and 3rd,
some internal discussion has to happen
Oh.
for dig deeper on the validation aspect
as well as the confirmation bit Rama
wanted to have, right?
We'll brainstorm it if I believe in,
I have high believe in Rama's proposal.
If he proposed something,
he might be having something in his brain.
I want to understand a bit better.
If that benefits, we'll have it.
Otherwise, later.
Yeah.
He's laughing. I am praising him,
but he's laughing.
No, no, no, no.
I was thinking in the past that people
Okay, so.
are typing and so that's right. Nothing,
nothing. Sorry, Tom.
I didn't mean to anything.
No, no, I am only typing wMio. So yeah,
I will put this wMio guys.
Haha.
Please go through it.
Tomorrow we'll discuss.
Sure, one, one,
one thing I want to clarify, Jyotish,
just, just sorry, Tom,
I know you are you are late delayed.
Huh?
Jyotish,
one thing when we say validation right,
we we there are three types of validation
in this you might have seen, right?
One is,
am I doing the job correctly or not,
right?
When I generate a DSL or when I ask the
questions?
Is there ambiguity like that?
So every node has a validation.
That is one type of validation, correct?
Jyotish, you got the point. The second.
So...
Ha, you finished, and then then I land.
Yeah, yeah.
Then there is a second type of validation.
The second type of validation is IWHA
specific, right? Do I have the account?
Do I have the project?
Do I have anything related to IWHA, right?
That can be more.
I'm not an expert on that, right?
Third is the service level validation.
Basically, oh, mapper is down.
right, those kind of things, right?
When I start itself, I think.
So the individual node level validation
happens independently after each and
every node has been completed. Got it?
The first level validation is,
is all the services up?
Am I able to get the account,
get the relevant details,
so that I can make an informed
conversation with the user?
Right,
so I won't show the output or anything to
the user.
Clear, sir.
Yes,
I think that's one difference between
No, okay.
Yeah.
flow service and workflow, right? I mean,
in the validation that I was talking
about is when you create a business view,
before you can see a technical view,
there's a validation whether you have the
right accounts and everything. If you do.
You will be then shown a technical view.
You can continue to make edits and at
Yeah.
some point when you are ready,
you will have to say create a workflow.
Earlier, we used to have a plan.
If you remember the older integration
agent also,
we had a plan UI on the chat itself,
right? It will stay. I'm doing step one,
step two, step 3,
and there has to be loaded.
That was earlier there,
so you had to start the flow workflow
creation,
but that has been removed because Bifrost
doesn't support that UI.
So now there's a simple next action which
says create workflow.
That is a second level confirmation that
the user is giving to yes, go ahead,
create something on the,
and that will be visible on your account.
Correct, correct. So, yeah, no,
same thing will be applicable here also,
So there are two level of validation.
Jyotish.
Jyotish, because see,
the account got to be there. Without that,
we cannot proceed.
The same what we are doing in workflow,
No, Prasad.
right? Account is available or not.
Prasad, give me,
I share my screen for a moment.
Yes.
What Jyotish is trying to explain is,
are you guys, can you, yeah.
Mhm.
Yes, we can see. Yes, yes.
So when the prompt is given,
it directly asks project, okay.
And after project,
it is asking certain more questions. Okay,
that is a questioning.
requirement gathering thing.
And once it is done, it say, okay,
Yeah.
use this project.
It has only created a business view,
not a technical view. Okay.
So only business view gets generated
first.
Right, this is what we want.
This is what we are saying.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, this is this is there,
but what what is happening now? See,
once business view is getting generated,
it says validate connector operation and
accounts. Basically,
in this whole business logic,
we have also given this is my operation
data, this is my...
application data. So this is nothing,
it's a planner only for us.
Now once we say continue, okay, continue,
validate it,
it immediately asks for account data and
also creates the technical view.
Correct, Sonal.
Okay.
Got it. No, my only point is,
sorry to interrupt, please can you say,
Okay.
my only point is creation of account,
validation of account and all internal.
I should not ask the user to validate the
connector operations account.
That is my headache. I have to take care.
What I have to validate,
ask him to validate this, can you...
Please approve my understanding of this
plan. That is all I have to validate.
Remaining and all, it's given.
I think.
I think wording should be changed,
Jyotish.
What do you feel like validate connector
operation and accounts?
Yeah,
I think this feedback has been given and
it was updated and now it is gone back.
So I don't know what's happening.
Okay, I think Ramu, you are also correct.
Like this is the same what we are
proposing, but instead of suggestion.
Well, I'm sorry, I did.
I again put a emoji of laughing.
Yeah.
Sorry in Jyotish.
I was just laughing along.
Yeah.
Nothing more than that. Yeah, go ahead.
If we,
so basically when we are saying suggested
action, okay,
we are preventing user to go to the next
course of action with yes, approval step,
okay. So, Jyotish,
Got it, got it.
the only point we need to bring over here
is with this flow creation,
we want an approval step.
before proceeding to technical view,
right? We need approval step.
Once user approves it,
then only we would be able to proceed
Yes.
with the next course of action,
and then the flow service will get
generated, apparently. But till here,
we have to see.
Yes.
So, this is I think same, right?
Yes,
I think that is that is something like
was earlier remember like during
launchpad we were discussing that no,
we will also show the technical view and
once like you know like without project
you can't show technical view,
but with project we'll show the technical
view and we'll do all these validations
internally,
like even what Drama is saying,
like you know,
I will not even ask the user.
But.
But when we,
when it was actually like created,
Yeah, yeah.
then we saw that there's a valuation step
that has been added,
because I think we couldn't do it
internally. Now,
if Rama is saying that we can do that,
I mean, I mean, we'll be very happy if we,
Mm.
No, no, not in, not in Thanmayi.
if not, I mean, then we can add a step.
I mean, whatever is possible,
Rama, yeah, Ramu is saying that, okay,
accounts are there, operations are there,
we can add a.
character is there. But accounts also,
let's assume if there are more than three
You know, no,
subsequently you have to ask.
accounts for the same application. Yeah.
That is fine.
Subsequently you have to ask.
That is there.
But what I'm trying to say here is I
Yes.
don't want to exhibit to the user.
I am validating connector like that.
What I'm going to say is I'm exhibiting
to the, I want to exhibit to the user.
I am validating or understanding your
problem statement.
Please confirm how I understood the
problem statement clearly.
That is the message I'm saying. However,
Jyotish knows the copy way better.
Correct, correct? No, no,
I think that should be there. Basically,
the validate plan is there, right? Sonal,
in workflow, there is some.
Mm.
Yes, yes, so this is validate, not plan.
It is basically, yeah,
user is OK with the current business view
and he's clicking on it to proceed with
Yeah.
the set course of set next tool calling
data, but but actually it is like...
Haha, correct, correct.
The option is coming as a suggested
action. Instead of that, it should be,
you know, restricting user, okay,
you have to say yes, no, or modify.
Any other intent apart from it.
What if user types in, okay,
there's some more work I need to do
related to the other workflow,
other flow service, okay?
The intent is itself is a different thing.
So how this agent will consider it in the
current context or the next context or
how it should be,
it should go back saying user that okay
Sonal, we will, yeah, yeah, we will,
we will internally discuss that, Sonal,
if you are.
but our thing, Prasad,
just to want to make sure,
sorry to cut you off, Sonal,
since we are there, Prasad,
Yeah.
do we got any update on the scrum,
because on the scrum you might have
discussed, right?
Did you get any update from connector
team, all the dependencies, because...
Rajat also discussed with me on a program
plan,
so I know he said he's discussing with
you as well.
So did we get that information, Prasad,
from the connector team,
Mhm.
from the IWHI conversion like DSL to XML,
all those things?
Mhm.
No, no,
that they say I will set up this call to
discuss all those things,
so we will discuss. We can see, yeah,
Four.
we we cannot have 10 different meetings
here, so it's very difficult to manage it.
Totally understood.
OK, so let the people join,
we will discuss all those dependencies
one by one. OK,
we'll try to conclude on UX.
I'll just add, yeah,
I'll just add one other point.
There was one suggested UX journey for
Launchpad, and Sonal is there,
so she's aware.
The version that we are seeing in the
agent is a little different from that,
right? So, I mean,
what we have to also align on next call
is, do we align it with...
with what we had initially proposed or we
align with what has gone live because I
think from launchpad also there might
there will be some tickets that will be
raised saying that it is not the designs
have been not been followed.
Now whether that's because of a technical
constraint right now and can be fixed
later on or we are just going to continue
with this I think that decision has to be
No.
taken and then we follow that because we
want both the experiences to be similar
but currently there are two.
Different versions, not very different,
but a little different version of
experiences which is there,
what is live versus what is been proposed.
So I just also wanted to call that out
and we can we can internally discuss that.
Pradeep.
I think things are still fluid.
I don't think we have anything is set in
Jyotish, yeah, yeah, one, one thing,
one thing, Jyotish,
Sure.
stone, but...
I would again request you.
I know I have been again and again saying
the challenge here is the flow guys are
all pure developer guys, right? So,
given given the developer persona,
we are concentrating on some areas.
One thing,
one thing I'm just thinking loud.
One thing is, once I give the prompt,
can we ask the user,
do you want a style A, style B?
I'm just telling as an example,
you can come up with a better copy.
Example I'm saying, style A or style B,
right? What does style A will do is,
it'll do a traditional SDLC.
Like I will gather the requirements,
I'll properly make sure I'll do all those
things and do that.
But how developers think is,
they also think in a different way.
They immediately start writing code,
right? I mean, most of the developers,
right? How they think, right?
And then they want to modify, modify,
or they feel, hey,
what is these questions, man?
Why are you asking me these questions?
I don't know.
You have to talk to a business analyst.
Like that they may think, right?
So can we show them upfront some DSL? Oh,
this is what I tried as a first shot,
but please tell me what is that you want
to modify so that they feel comfortable.
Because when you ask some business
questions, they may not feel comfortable.
I'm just thinking loud, please.
I'm not saying we have to do that.
So we will ask the user, do you want to?
Core developer example I'm saying,
style A or style B. Style A would be,
I'll be asking him technical questions,
business questions,
and maybe irritate him.
Or I go with style B,
where I'll first do whatever that comes
into my mind and ask the user to modify.
And I will tell them upfront, hey,
from what you gave, it is there.
But there are some clarifications
required.
Either you look into it and modify that
or I can ask you some clarification
questions and we can we can work to it.
So this is some thought process I want to
Yeah.
bring it up.
Please think about that as well.
Yeah. No, thanks.
That's a good input because see,
Launchpad was designed mostly for
business users, right?
And it was not supposed to support
technical users, but now, like,
we have to cater to both.
So that's a good point.
We'll definitely think about it.
But having said that, also,
Yeah.
that's why I asked the question,
who is a persona?
Times at 100% technical users,
but like it could also be a mixed user,
right?
Because we user will have access to
Launchpad,
could be a business user who might just
end up landing on a on this flow,
like where they building a flow service,
Right, right, right, right, right.
so I mean we'll have to somehow bring
some balance.
No, what what I would what? Yeah, no,
what what I would suggest for Q3, right?
We will go ahead,
have a one fixed personnel. OK,
we can introduce tiles and all definitely
later,
but we will have see the the way we have
decided, right?
One static way to get into the flow agent.
Similarly,
we'll have predefined flow decided for Q3
and we'll move ahead.
We can introduce the variation styles
definitely. Yeah.
Prasad, that is not a big,
big change from a coding perspective,
but think about the impact,
think about the impact will bring in,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Ramu,
from no, no, no, Ramu,
because...
the problem from coding it may be very
easy. OK,
see converging into all these user
journeys and all will become a lot of
time if you start different variations.
That's my.
This is not for you.
I think it will be applicable for entire
Launchpad experience. Like as a user,
if I am enrolled,
my persona should also be get registered
with Launchpad experience. I mean,
Yeah, correct.
it's for all the agents,
not only for integration agent.
This problem is there,
but there was a focus always that
Yeah, yeah.
business user will be using the Launchpad
experience and for business users only.
We are making this, so I think...
No, no,
I'm just trying to narrow the scope.
That's it.
I am not denying all your ideas.
No, no, totally understood, Prasad.
My only concern is, you know,
think of it right. If I give this to,
let's say, Jayesh or Ramu or anyone,
right, what they would want is,
and if you ask Ramu or Jayesh a question
like, oh, tell me a business question,
I don't know whether they'll be super
happy to answer that business question.
Right, but when you show the final output,
the code, they are super expert in that.
They'll say, "Ah,
there is a if condition missed,
there is no else part. OK,
then they will say, 'Hey,
can you add an else part?
That is what I I'm more concerned on on
on this, because I was...
No, but the no, no, no.
The question here is that is that the
path by default you want to implement for
Flow Agent? OK.
No, we will ask the user,
we'll ask the user as a first to one
question,
so that it is a technical persona,
but you have two paths.
One path is like this,
another path is like this, right?
And once the user chooses the second path,
I will always, I mean,
Ashok knows or Sonal knows better.
They store it in cookie or whatever it is,
and subsequently we will continue to use
the same thing.
So it's just a one-time.
You are talking about two different
journeys, right?
So what? I'm definitely with you, Ramu.
Like, yes, yes, but for the same persona,
I'm not changing the persona.
A different styles, OK, different styles,
but is it to two different paths within
the journey?
Got it.
Correct. So what I'm saying,
limit the scope for now to one path.
Got it.
Whatever the path you want,
let's limit to one path.
Means in terms of a scope,
I am trying to constrain you people.
No, totally understood, Prasad.
End of the day, it's a products call,
product and the UX Jyotish call.
If they say, yeah, yeah,
it's going to be one path and follow this
path, we are going to do that.
But I just want to throw it around.
Sure, sure, okay.
Okay, fine, I think.
One thing, sorry, Ramu, I mean,
if it is it possible for you, and I mean,
if you know some ******** technical users,
can you ask them to use the close of the
That is the intention.
That is the intention, Jyotish.
workflow?
I requested Sonal.
Sonal is working on to put it in Dev Ops
and I have identified some persons and I
also spoke to them and spoke to Rinku
team and other things.
So we have identified some core people
and those people I want to play for two
weeks, like give it to them, let them,
let them.
play with it and give us the feedback.
Totally aligned with you.
Workflow, right?
What? No, no, floor.
Can you also tell them to use workflow?
I just want to see like,
because like the entire launchpad was
built for business users.
I want to see like,
because if they face issue using that,
right, they will also face,
probably face issue when we are building.
I can give you,
I can give you the persons because I
cannot go and ask another favor,
so you can ask.
Sure, sure, sure. I mean,
we can reach out.
It'll be really interesting to see
because we're also doing some user
testing later this month. And we,
but maybe those are business users,
but let's see if we find some technical
users.
But Jyotish,
there are certain criteria like from when
we onboard right user to this particular
tenant.
So we have certain roles already given
like and there was a discussion happening
around with Jay Gauthier and team about
adding persona. Okay.
that whether it's an integration
specialist or is it a business user or it
Mm.
is non-technical user or something.
So you can have this discussion again
Okay.
with Gabe and everyone because when this
launchpad or BSoft was started, it was,
I mean,
from that time we were discussing it and
then.
Suddenly,
the focus went to only business user.
Yeah,
but but now the now the we we are not
focusing on business users only, right?
Because we are saying that it will be for
technical business users, right?
Yes, technical integration specialist,
basically they know everything.
Yeah.
So for simple,
they will never come to our system.
And flow, what I've heard,
only technical people are using it,
like integration specialist and more.
So if we have to keep that persona thing
in mind, then we have to discuss it.
In broader group, like...
For because it is binded to the user,
right user data.
The.
So, user profile data, so...
M.
But now we don't have any concept of
persona right now.
And we were planning to set personas,
but we are not doing that anymore, right?
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, I'll stop recording, I think.
Yeah.